themes4all.com 2018-02-20

# Privacy Policy | Themes4all - WordPress Premium Templates

Your privacy is important to us. This document about the protection of personal data describes how we collect and use personal data that you provide us with on our website. It also provides information on how to update them.

We will not sell, share, trade, or rent this information to others in ways inconsistent with this statement.

If you have any question about this Private Policy, please contact us at [support@themes4all.com](mailto:support@themes4all.com)

## Information Collection and Use

**We collect following information:**

  * Contact information (name, postal address, email address, etc.)
  * Unique log in information (username, password, user ID)
  * Credit/Debit Card Information
  * Other information (your orders)
  * Browser type, entering page, IP address, etc. (to create website visitor statistics)

**We use this information to:**

  * Complete your order,
  * Answer your requirements,
  * Answer your questions or queries.

## How we use your personal data

We use the personal data that you provide us with only to receive an order and to complete it. We do not share your personal information with third parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the online payment gateway GP WebPay (maintained by [Global Payments Inc.](http://www.globalpaymentsinc.com/Europe/Czech/productsServices/eCommerce.html)) for payment. It has its own Privacy Policy available on the official website.

## Data security

We have introduced appropriate physical, electronic and management methods to protect your personal data.

## Children‘s Privacy

The content of our website is not directed at children under the age of 15. That is why we neither collect nor keep information about such persons.

## Newsletter

You will receive our Newsletter, until you unsubscribed through email. How to unsubscribe is in all our emails.

## How to access or change your information

You can edit your registration email address, username and password in the Members area. If you want to access information we have collected about you or change information other than the above listed, write to [support@themes4all.com](mailto:support@themes4all.com). Appropriate steps will be taken to verify your identity before you’ll be granted access to your information and able to make changes. In this way, we can ensure better protection of your personal data.
